okay here we go
um
and once a day I'd like you to do the
seven the improve a few
if you're not sure ask cat okay
foreign
[Music]
so you can use
floor to the temple here
and thank them
try to imagine what they look like
then imagine where they broke
um
somebody took your money
somebody made the money somebody made uh
focused
[Music]
somebody brought the vegetables
foreign
[Music]
they have a right to some of our demons
this is a second meditation that I'd
like you to do today
the idea
[Music]
how did that idea start
Ed
[Music]
yourself
mentally
[Music]
um
in business
[Music]
foreign
how do you think
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
physically
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
from
uh
moisture
[Music]
um
possible
[Music]
um
everything
is
[Music]
not available
one person
watching it is
foreign
[Music]